giftcardgranny.com 2019-10-22

# Privacy Policy - Gift Card Granny

_ _ **Updated May 2019**

This Privacy Statement applies to information that Gift Card Granny, LLC, on behalf of itself and its corporate affiliates (collectively “Gift Card Granny,” “GCG,” “we” or “us”) collects on www.GiftCardGranny.com and other websites, applications, and digital services (collectively, the “Site”) on or to which this Privacy Statement is linked or referenced (collectively, the “ **Services** ”).

Your privacy is important to us. This GCG Privacy Statement (“ **Privacy Statement”** ) describes the information we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with the information we collect from or about you through the Services. This Privacy Statement does not apply to third-party websites and other digital services linked to the Services or information collected from you off line. 

The Services are intended for U.S. residents who are the age of majority or older in their place of residence (age 21 in Mississippi, age 19 in Alabama and Nebraska and age 18 in other states and Washington, D.C.).  You are not authorized to access and use the Services if you are located outside the U.S., or are younger than the age of majority. 

This Privacy Statement is incorporated into and made a part of the GCG Website Terms of Use (“ **Terms of Use** ”) and the customer Terms of Service (“ **Terms of Service** ”). 

 **If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Statement, our Terms of Use, or, if applicable, our Terms of Service, then please do not use**  www.GiftCardGranny.com.

 **How We Define Personal Information**

For purposes of this Privacy Statement, “ **Personal Information** ” means any information that identifies a specific person.  For example, Personal Information includes name, address, phone number, email address, the last four digits of a Social Security number, etc.  Personal Information also includes information that does not directly identify you but when combined with other information identifies (or can be used to identify) you. 

 **How  We Collect and Use Your Personal Information **

How we collect and use information from you depends on how and why you use the Services. GCG collects information in the following ways:

 _When You Give GCG Information_ **:**  When you create an account, we may ask you for Personal Information including (but not necessarily limited to) name, email address, telephone number, and credit card or debit card number and associated card security code. Certain parts of the Services may require users to provide contact information (such as name and e-mail address), demographic information (such as ZIP code), financial information (such as credit card number and/or bank account and routing number) and other similar information. If you sign up for emails about GCG’s latest news and new products, we collect the email address that you give us. We also collect feedback, questions, and information that you provide to us for customer support.

 _When You Use the Services_ : ** ** We collect information about how and when you use the Services:

 ** _Through Server Logs_** : A server log is a list of the activities that a server performs. GCG’s servers automatically collect and store in server logs, your search queries, Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time of your request and referral URL, and certain cookies that identify your browser or GCG account. 

 ** _From Your Computer, Tablet or Mobile Telephone_** : We may collect information about your computer, tablet or mobile telephone (“ **Device** ”), such as model, operating system version, mobile network information, telephone number, internet service provider and similar identifiers.  We may associate your Device information with your account.  We may collect and store information (including Personal Information) on your Device through browser web storage (including HTML 5) and web application data caches.

We may collect data about the location of the Device that you use to access the Services (“ **Location Data** ”) using IP address, GPS, cellular towers and other information from your mobile service provider, Bluetooth address, Wi-Fi access points and information made available by you or others that indicates the current or prior location of the user, such as geotag information in photographs.  How we collect Location Data depends on how you access the Services.  Certain Services may collect Location Data even when you are not actively using the Services.  If you do not want us to collect Location Data from your mobile Device, please turn off the location services in your Device settings.

 ** _Through Mobile Applications (“Apps”)_** : We may from time to time collect information about your use of and interaction with the App, such as your Device’s operating system, browser type, domain and other system settings, search queries, the country and time zone in which your Device is located, metadata and other information associated with files stored on your Device.

 ** _Through Cookies and Similar Tools_** : We use cookies, pixel tabs (also known as web beacons, flash cookies and clear GIFs) and similar technology to automatically collect information about you when you use the Services. Please read the “How We Use Data Collection Tools” section (below) to learn more about how GCG uses these tools.

 _From Other Sources_ : GCG collects information about you from third parties:

 ** _When you Connect with Social Media through the Services_** _:_  The Services link to social media platforms through “plug-ins” (e.g., Twitter and LinkedIn buttons). When you are logged into your social media account and access the Services, we may (depending on your settings) automatically receive information (including Personal Information) from the social media platform.  GCG collects and uses this information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement or at the time the information is collected. Please remember that the manner in which a social media platform uses, stores and discloses your information is governed by the terms and policies applicable to your use of such platforms, and GCG has no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any social media platform with which you connect through the App or Services.

 ** _From Third Parties_** _:_  GCG may from time to time supplement the information that we collect from you with information from third parties. We may combine the third-party information with information that we already have from or about you.

 ** _Through Service Providers_** : Third parties that assist us with our business operations also collect and use information (including Personal Information) through the Services and also may share the collected information with us. For example, our service providers collect and share information with us to analyze the performance of the Services and detect and prevent fraud.

 **GCG uses your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Statement and for any other purpose that we disclose when we collect your Personal Information**. 

GCG uses Personal Information to:

  * • identify you when you access and use the Services and personalize your experience of the Services;
  * • respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests for information, products or services;
  * • verify your identity;
  * • deliver advertisements and marketing communications to you;
  * • help us understand the types of products and services that interest you and present you with offers for them;
  * • provide you with important notices about our products and policies or other administrative information;
  * • evaluate your eligibility for products or services;
  * • conduct data analysis, identify usage trends and determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns;
  * • develop and improve the Services and our products and services;
  * • detect and prevent fraud;
  * • comply with applicable laws and regulations and legal process and law enforcement requirements; and
  * • enforce the Terms of Use, Terms of Service, and our other contracts with you.

If you provide GCG with access to your credit or debit card, and/or to any financial institution account, in connection or pursuant to the Services, you authorize us to collect and store your credit card, debit card, and/or financial institution account information, along with other information related to your qualifying transaction, such as purchase amount, purchase time, purchase date, and merchant for each transaction with the applicable card payment network or financial institution. As with other Personal Information, we may use that information in connection with the reason for which it was provided.

 **How We Use Data Collection Tools**

Cookies, pixel tabs (also known as web beacons, flash cookies and clear GIFs) and similar technology (“ **Data Collection Tools** ”) help GCG automatically collect information about you when you use the Services.

 ** _Web Beacons_** : A web beacon (also called a pixel tag or clear GIF) is computer code that communicates information from your device to a server.  Some of our content and emails may contain embedded web beacons that allow a server to read certain types of information from your Device, allow us to count the number of people who have viewed content, to know when you opened an email message, and the IP address of your Device.  Web beacons help us develop statistical information to provide better and more personalized content.

 ** _Cookies_** :  Cookies are small text files that are sent to or accessed from your web browser or your computer’s hard drive. A cookie typically contains the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie originated, the “lifetime” of the cookie (i.e., when it expires), and a randomly generated unique number or similar identifier. A cookie also may contain information about your Device, such as user settings, browsing history, and activities conducted while using the Services.  

GCG uses the following types of cookies:

  * • Strictly necessary cookies, which are required for the operation of the Services. Without them, for example, you would not be able to register or log in for the Services that GCG offers.
  * • Analytical/performance cookies, which allow GCG to recognize and count the number of visitors, learn how visitors navigate the Services, and improve the Services.
  * • Functionality cookies, which GCG uses to recognize you when you return to the Services.
  * • Targeting cookies, which record your visits to the Services, the pages you visited, and the links you followed. Targeting cookies helps GCG deliver digital advertisements that are targeted to your interests (as inferred from your online activity). GCG also shares information collected through targeting cookies with third parties that send you targeted advertisements.
  * • Interaction cookies, which allow you to connect GCG through social media.

To learn more about cookies and web beacons, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

Data Collection Tools record how long you spend on various webpages, which webpages you view, your search queries, the products you viewed, error and performance reports, your IP address, your browser type, time zone and language settings and operating system.  Data Collection Tools also help us with fraud prevention and detection.

GCG also may use analytics services, such as Google Analytics, to collect information.  Generally, analytics services do not identify individual users.  Many analytics services allow you to opt out of data collection.  For example, to learn more about Google Analytics practices and to opt out, visit [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads "Google Ad Settings") or download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

 ** _Your Control of Data Collection Technology_** **:** Some web and mobile browsers provide settings that allow you to control or reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is stored in your browser. If you set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of the Services or access some of our online services. You also may be able to reject use of mobile device identifiers by activating the appropriate setting on your Device.  Although you are not required to accept cookies or mobile device identifiers, if you block or reject them, you may not have access to all features available through the Services.

 **How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Chrome) incorporate a “Do Not Track” (“ **DNT** ”) or similar feature that signals to a website that a user does not want to have his or her online activity and behavior tracked.  If a website that responds to a particular DNT signal receives the DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser’s user.  Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform.  For this reason, many website operators, including GCG, do not respond to DNT signals. GCG is able to offer and provide you with our Services whether or not your browser incorporates DNT signals.

 **How  We Share Personal Information **

We may share Personal Information collected through the Services as follows.

 _Affiliates_ : GCG shares Personal Information within GCG’s corporate family for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement and as required by law.

 _Service Providers_ : GCG shares information with GCG’s third-party service providers that help us operate the Services, provide GCG products, and personalize your experience on the Services. Some service providers help us with payment processing, facilitating payments, sending emails, order fulfillment, conducting advertising, providing customer service or product support, industry benchmarking, consumer analysis, market research, and administering promotions.

 _Corporate Transactions_ : GCG may share and transfer Personal Information if GCG is involved in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy, or other change of ownership or control by GCG or any affiliated company (in each case, whether in whole or in part).

 _Other Lawful Disclosures_ : GCG also shares information: (i) as permitted by law; (ii) if we determine that disclosure of specific information is necessary to comply with the request of a law enforcement or regulatory agency or other legal process; (iii) to protect the rights, privacy, property, interests, or safety of our company or our affiliates, customers, business partners, employees, or the general public; (iv) to pursue available remedies or limit the damages; (v) to enforce the Terms of Use and Terms of Service; and (vi) to respond to an emergency.

GCG never publicly discloses any Personal Information related to financial or payment activities or any government identification numbers. GCG also doesn't allow unauthorized publishing or disclosure of any user’s non-public contacts.

 **How We Protect and Store Information**

GCG takes precautions intended to help protect information that we collect and store; however, any transmission to us is at your own risk, and we expect that you will use appropriate security measures to protect your information.

You are responsible for maintaining the security of your account credentials and other authentication involved in obtaining access to password-protected or secure areas of the Services.  GCG will treat access to the Services through your account credentials as authorized by you.  Unauthorized access to password-protected or secure areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution.  We may suspend your use of all or part of the Services without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security.  If you believe that information you provided to us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately using the contact information provided below.

We retain information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which you provided the information, to comply with legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce agreements, and similar essential purposes.

APPLE DEVICE ADDITIONAL TERMS

If you access an App via a Mobile Device or tablet branded by Apple, Inc. (“ **Apple** ”) and running Apple’s iOS (an “ **Apple Device** ”), the following terms (“ **Apple Device Additional Terms** ”) are hereby made part of this Privacy Statement: (a) If this Privacy Statement or any agreement between GCG and you conflict with the Apple Device Additional Terms, then the Apple Device Additional Terms shall apply with respect to access and use of the Services via an Apple Device.; (b) You acknowledge that this Privacy Statement or your agreements with GCG about the Services are not an agreement with Apple. GCG, not Apple, is solely responsible for any App you access via your Apple Device (“ **iOS App** ”) and the content thereof.  If this Privacy Statement or your agreements with GCG about the Services are less restrictive with respect to an iOS App or otherwise conflict with, the Apple App Store Terms of Service (the “ **App Store Terms of Service** ”), the App Store Terms of Service shall apply to the extent of any conflict.; (c) The license granted to use an iOS App is limited to a non-transferable license to use the App on an Apple Device that you own or control and as permitted by the usage rules set forth in the App Store Terms of Service.; (d) GCG is solely responsible for providing any maintenance and support services for an iOS App.  You acknowledge that Apple has no obligation whatsoever to furnish any maintenance and support services with respect to any iOS App.; (e) GCG is solely responsible for any product warranty, whether express or implied by law, to the extent not effectively disclaimed.  If an iOS App fails to conform to any applicable warranty, you may notify Apple and Apple will refund the purchase price for the iOS App (if any) and, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Apple will have no other warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to the iOS App and all other claims, losses, liabilities, damages, costs or expenses attributable to any failure to conform to any warranty are GCG’ sole responsibility.; (f) You hereby acknowledge that GCG, not Apple, is responsible for addressing your or any third-party claims relating to an iOS App and/or use of an iOS App, including, but not limited to: (i) product liability claims; (ii) any claim that an iOS App fails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and (iii) claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation. This Privacy Statement or your agreements with GCG about the Services do not limit GCG’s liability beyond what is permitted by applicable law.; and (g) You acknowledge that, in the event of any third party claim that an iOS or your possession and use of an iOS App infringes that third party’s intellectual property rights, GCG, not Apple, is solely responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement and discharge of any such intellectual property infringement claim.

 **Linking to Other Sites**

GCG may provide links to websites operated by unrelated third parties, such as companies that provide services for us or in which we think you may have an interest.  Please note that when you navigate to the website of an unrelated third party, this Privacy Statement no longer applies.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website or service that you visit to understand how your Personal Information is processed.

 **Exclusions  
** This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information collected by GCG other than Personal Information collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to GCG through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and GCG shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

 **How Can I Correct or Delete My Personal Information?**  

If you would like to correct or delete Personal Information, please send us an e-mail with your request to [info@giftcardgranny.com](mailto:info@giftcardgranny.com "Gift Card Granny Email Address").  GCG reserves the right to request that you provide information that will enable GCG to confirm that you have the authority to correct or delete the Personal Information that you want corrected or deleted. GCG will use reasonable efforts to correct your Personal Information but may not be able to correct or delete Personal Information shared with third parties.

 **Your Opt Out Rights**

 ** _SMS Notifications:_** To the extent you access the Service through a mobile device, and by acknowledging our Terms of Service, you consent to our communicating with you on your mobile device, including through the use of an automatic telephone dialing system or a prerecorded or artificial voice, by SMS, MMS, text message or other electronic means and that certain information about your usage of the products and features may be communicated to us. You are not required to enter into this agreement as a condition of using the Service. By providing us with a telephone number, you expressly waive any protections afforded to you under federal, state, or corporate Do Not Call lists for the purpose of receiving telephone calls or text messages from us related to your use of the Service.  By providing us with a telephone number, you represent and warrant that you are the authorized subscriber to that telephone number and that you have the authority to provide consent to be contacted at that telephone number.  If you would like to revoke this consent at any time, you may do so by contacting us through your account profile at https://www.giftcardgranny.com/contact/. You also may opt out through your GCG account or otherwise according to instructions included in the communication you receive (for example, replying “STOP” to an SMS message).

 ** _Unsubscribe from Our E-mails_** **:**  If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails from us, (whether on our behalf or on behalf of a third party), including our e-newsletters, follow the unsubscribe process at the bottom of the promotional e-mail. Note that even if you opt out, you may still receive transactional e-mails from us (e.g., e-mails related to the completion of your registration, correction of user data, password reset requests, reminder e-mails that you have requested, and any other similar communications essential to your transactions on or made through the services).

If you have any problems or questions regarding your privacy preferences or opt out options, you may reach us during regular business hours at (866) 739-4914.

 ** _Your California Privacy Rights: A Notice to California Users (California Civil Code Section 1798.83)_**

Pursuant to California privacy law, registered users under 18 years of age may request to have content or information posted by the user removed from any of our online platforms. In order to effectuate removal of such content or information, you may reach us during regular business hours at (866) 739-4914.

The removal of content does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on any of our online platforms by the registered user.

We do not advertise or market any of the products or services identified in Chapter 22.1 Sec. 22580 (i) to users we have actual knowledge are under 18 years of age.

 **Children’s Privacy**

The Services are not directed to or intended for use by minors. Consistent with the requirements of the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, if we learn that we have received any information directly from a child under age 13 without his or her parent’s verified consent, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or his or her parent or legal guardian) to inform the child that he or she cannot use the Services and subsequently will delete that information.

 **Integrating Social Networking Services**  
You may have the option of posting your Services activities to social media platforms when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers, and subscribers on any social media platforms you have enabled will be able to view such activity.  

 **Notice to California Residents**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits individual California residents to opt-out of GCG’s disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. GCG currently does not disclose Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The Effective Date of this Privacy Statement is set forth at the top of this webpage. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement as business needs require. If we make material changes to the way we use Personal Information, we will post a notice about the changes prominently on the Services in advance so that you have an opportunity to discontinue your use of the Services. Your continued use of the Services after the Effective Date constitutes your acceptance of the amended Privacy Statement. The amended Privacy Statement supersedes all previous versions.

 **How to Contact Us**

If at any time you have questions about the GCG Privacy Statement, please contact us at [info@giftcardgranny.com ](mailto:info@giftcardgranny.com "Gift Card Granny Email Address")or by mail to GCG at 495 Mansfield Avenue Pittsburgh PA 15205.

© 2019 Gift Card Granny, LLC
